Gimme.
Barangnya.
Enjoy.
Nikmatilah.
Thanks.
Terima kasih.
What the hell!
Apa-apaan?
Who is that? Is he okay?
Siapa itu? Apa dia baik-baik saja?
He's out of it.
Dia tak sadar.
He's high out of his mind.
Dia mabuk berat.
Hey!
Hei!
Sir, you need to control yourself.
Pak, kendalikan dirimu.
Hand over the cocaine.
Berikan aku kokaina.
Not unless you have the cash for it.
Tidak, kecuali kau punya uang.
Just give it to me!
Berikan padaku!
Quit it and get out!
Hentikan. Pergilah!
Hey!
Hei!
What are you doing?
Apa yang kau lakukan?
Shut the hell up!
Diam!
It hurts!
Sakit!
That's freaky.
Menyeramkan.
Should we call the police?
Apa harus telepon polisi?
Or an ambulance.
Atau ambulans?
Damn amateur.
Dasar amatir.
Learn some restraint.
Belajarlah menahan diri.
WHERE IN ROPPONGI IS THIS? THIS IS CRAZY
INI ROPPONGI MANA? GILA
CAN'T BELIEVE WE CAN SEE THIS LIVE THE COMMENTS WON'T STOP LOL
TIDAK SANGKA BISA LIHAT LANGSUNG KOMENTARNYA RAMAI SEKALI HAHA
THIS CLUB WILL GET CLOSED DOWN
KELAB INI AKAN DITUTUP
Stimulants, narcotics, cannabis.
Stimulan, narkotika, ganja.
People who have used these drugs
Orang yang memakai obat-obatan itu
are now estimated to total two million in Japan.
totalnya kini diperkirakan mencapai dua juta di Jepang.
The number of people arrested for drug-related offenses
Jumlah orang yang ditangkap karena pelanggaran terkait narkoba
is as many as 14,000 yearly.
mencapai 14.000 per tahun.
Igarashi is the guy who got nabbed for marijuana before, right?
Igarashi ini pernah ditangkap karena ganja, 'kan?
And then cocaine and meth.
Juga, kokaina dan sabu-sabu.
What a stereotypical scumbag.
Memang berandal.
It's horrible what he did to that woman.
Yang dia lakukan pada wanita itu sungguh keji.
I feel sorry for the bereaved families
Aku kasihan pada keluarga korban
when people like this kill someone and get a light sentence
saat orang seperti ini membunuh, lalu dapat hukuman ringan
due to impaired mental capacity.
karena mental yang bermasalah.
That's absolutely unacceptable!
Itu tak bisa diterima!
Don't get mad at me.
Jangan marah padaku.
That said, if that Mad Dog finds out about this case,
Tapi jika Mad Dog tahu soal kasus ini,
things will get out of hand quickly.
keadaan akan menjadi kacau.
Excuse me, which division are you from?
Maaf, kau dari divisi mana?
I'm not with the police.
Aku bukan polisi.
Well, that's a problem. Did no one stop you from coming in?
Itu masalahnya. Apa tak ada yang mencegahmu masuk?
Only authorized personnel are--
Hanya pihak berwenang yang boleh…
I'm Kurosaki, a narcotics agent.
Aku Kurosaki, agen narkotika.
Excuse us, sir.
Maaf, Pak.
According to eyewitnesses, he collapsed right after inhaling the cocaine.
Menurut saksi mata, dia pingsan tepat setelah mengisap kokaina.
So the drug caused his death.
Jadi, kematiannya karena narkoba.
What?
Apa?
Why are you here?
Mau apa kau di sini?
To investigate, obviously.
Tentu saja untuk menyelidiki.
The NCD can sit this one out.
NCD tak perlu ikut campur kasus ini.
Not as long as cocaine is involved.
Tidak bisa selama kokaina terlibat.
This was a serial stabbing.
Ini penusukan berantai.
The perpetrator died due to an overdose, so the police get jurisdiction.
Pelaku meninggal karena overdosis. Jadi, polisi dapat yurisdiksi.
You've got to cuff them while they're still alive, you know.
Seharusnya tangkap dia sebelum mati.
Then get this over with quickly,
Maka cepatlah selesaikan,
police mutt.
Kacung Polisi.
Get lost,
Pergilah,
Ministry mutt.
Kacung Menteri.
Let the police handle this, dumbass.
Biar polisi yang urus ini, Bodoh.
Igarashi, you bastard!
Igarashi, berengsek!
Causing all this mess.
Membuat masalah saja.
What if they start investigating us too?
Bagaimana jika kita juga mulai diselidiki?
Hey.
Hei.
Oh, are you the Mr. Jellyfish who contacted me?
Kau Tuan Ubur-Ubur yang menghubungiku?
Yes.
Ya.
0.2 of speed, right? First time offer. Let's go with ten.
Sabu-sabu 0,2 gram, 'kan? Harga perdana. Sepuluh saja.
Ten? You mean 10,000 yen?
Sepuluh? Maksudmu 10.000 yen?
You're a kid.
Kau masih kecil.
Are you an idiot?
Kau bodoh, ya?
Kids shouldn't be buying speed.
Anak-anak tak boleh beli sabu-sabu.
Listen up.
Dengar.
You try this just once and there's no going back.
Jika coba ini sekali, kau akan kecanduan.
Your family, your friends…
Keluargamu, teman-temanmu…
You'll lose them all.
Kau akan kehilangan mereka.
Why is a dealer lecturing me?
Kenapa pengedar malah menceramahiku?
Shut it.
Diam.
Go eat a hamburger, kid. Then get fat and sleep!
Belilah hamburger saja, Dik. Agar kau gemuk, lalu tidur!
Wait.
Tunggu.
Crap, what am I doing?
Sial, apa yang kulakukan?
Can't do math 'cause you never went to high school?
Apa kau tak bisa berhitung karena tak SMA?
Piece of shit.
Berengsek.
I'm sorry.
Maafkan aku.
But two million per month is a bit much.
Tapi dua juta per bulan kebanyakan.
Don't speak.
Jangan bicara.
Sorry.
Maaf.
I told you not to speak!
Kubilang jangan bicara!
Come on now.
Ayolah.
Enough with the overacting.
Jangan berlebihan.
I guess you just can't forget the good ol' acting days, huh?
Kau tak bisa melupakan masa-masa jaya berakting, ya?
You know what, fine.
Baiklah.
I'll give you a scene to act.
Kuberikan kau adegan untuk berakting.
Go on. Drink this.
Ayo. Minum ini.
What? But…
Apa? Tapi…
-That's… -Ready?
- Itu… - Siap?
Action.
Akting.
Please let me off.
Tolong lepaskan aku.
There.
Ayo.
Ready?
Siap?
Action.
Akting.
Good stuff, huh?
Keren, 'kan?
That's a good expression for a washed-up former actor.
Ekspresinya bagus untuk aktor yang sudah tak laku.
Let's get another angle next, yeah?
Ayo coba sudut lain, ya?
What's with those eyes?
Kenapa menatapku?
Did you forget who gave your debt-ridden ass some work?
Apa kau lupa siapa yang memberimu pekerjaan saat terlilit utang?
It was me.
Aku.
You've been knee-deep in crime all this time.
Kau sudah berkubang dalam kejahatan.
Don't start thinking you can escape.
Jangan pikir kau bisa lepas.
Two days!
Dua hari!
Get me the rest of the money.
Berikan sisa uangnya padaku.
Go sell an eyeball or a kidney if you have to!
Jual bola mata atau ginjalmu bila perlu!
What? You got a problem?
Apa? Kau keberatan?
No, sir.
Tidak.
Hey, come out!
Hei, keluar!
Quiet!
Diam!
I'm here to collect.
Aku mau menagih uang.
Don't be so loud.
Jangan keras-keras.
If you don't pay up, I'm going to lose my damn organs!
Jika kau tak bayar, aku bisa kehilangan organ tubuhku!
-Get in. -What?
- Masuk. - Apa?
Get in!
Masuk!
It stinks!
Bau sekali!
Keep this open!
Buka saja!
-Stop! -What?
- Hentikan! - Apa?
God knows who's watching and from where.
Siapa pun bisa mengawasi kita.
Guys from all over are trying to get me dead.
Banyak pihak yang mau aku mati.
This again?
Ini lagi?
You're just being paranoid.
Kau hanya paranoid.
No.
Tidak.
Just the other day, there was a sniper aiming for me from across the river.
Tempo hari, ada penembak jitu membidikku dari seberang sungai.
You would be dead already if that was true.
Kau sudah mati jika itu benar.
Why would a sniper go after a homeless old man like you?
Untuk apa penembak jitu mengincar tunawisma tua sepertimu?
Don't change the topic.
Jangan mengubah topik.
I didn't.
Tidak.
Forget all that.
Lupakan saja.
You did bring it, didn't you?
Kau bawa barangnya, 'kan?
Here.
Ini.
It's ice, not speed.
Ini kristal, bukan bubuk.
Ice, huh?
Kristal, ya?
Hey!
Hei!
Pay up for this month first.
Bayar dulu untuk yang bulan ini.
What?
Apa?
Hey, this is nowhere near enough.
Hei, ini masih kurang banyak.
Take any valuables.
Ambil saja barang yang berharga.
What?
Apa?
Like what?
Apa misalnya?
Valuables?
Berharga?
Wait, you have a son?
Tunggu, kau punya anak?
That? Just throw it away for me.
Itu? Buangkan saja.
Chiaki…
Chiaki…
Takeru!
Takeru!
Can I even get anything for this?
Memangnya ini akan laku kujual?
Where's Kurosaki when we need him?
Di mana Kurosaki saat dibutuhkan?
He hasn't checked in, as per usual.
Dia belum mengabari, seperti biasa.
-Screw that! -Why are you yelling at me?
- Persetan! - Kenapa kau memarahiku?
I know where Igarashi got the cocaine.
Aku tahu dari mana Igarashi dapat kokaina.
You went off on your own again?
Kau bertindak sendiri lagi?
You can't just be biting at everything.
Kau tak bisa asal bertindak.
That's why they call you Mad Dog!
Makanya kau dijuluki Mad Dog!
He's just a stray dog with a sharp nose.
Dia hanya anjing liar yang hidungnya tajam.
What's the address?
Di mana alamatnya?
Room 203, Yuzuki Apartments, 3-Chome, Nerima City.
Apartemen Yuzuki nomor 203, 3-Chome, Kota Nerima.
They're probably just cogs in the machine, anyway.
Mungkin mereka hanya roda-roda kecil.
Mr. Inaba, the cogs will lead us to the machine.
Pak Inaba, roda-roda ini akan menuntun kita ke mesinnya.
What does that mean?
Apa artinya?
I shouldn't have to tell you,
Seharusnya aku tak bilang,
but for our pride as the NCD, don't let the police get ahead of us!
tapi demi harga diri kita sebagai NCD, jangan biarkan polisi duluan.
Yes, sir!
Baik!
Mr. Kyonosuke, I finished 40 bags.
Pak Kyonosuke, aku sudah selesai 40 kantong.
-Is that enough for the 0.1 net bags? -Yes.
- Apa cukup untuk 0,1 gram bersih? - Ya.
Make 20 bags of one gram gross next.
Selanjutnya, buat 20 kantong satu gram bersih.
Okay.
Baik.
Hey, hands off the merchandise!
Hei, jangan sentuh barang jualan!
Relax, I paid for it.
Tenang, aku bayar.
Want some?
Mau?
I don't use it. I just sell it.
Aku tak pakai. Hanya menjual.
Hey, you! I told you to use water.
Hei, kau! Sudah kubilang pakai air!
Yes, but that's kind of a pain.
Ya, tapi itu merepotkan.
If a customer gets busted, they'll do DNA tests on that.
Jika ada pelanggan tertangkap, polisi akan melakukan tes DNA.
Can't we just use a courier service?
Apa tak bisa pakai jasa kurir saja?
Use your brain.
Pakai otakmu.
Regular mail is harder to track down compared to a courier.
Pos biasa lebih sulit dilacak dibanding kurir.
You amateur!
Dasar amatir!
What's up?
Ada apa?
Hey. How did it go?
Hei. Bagaimana?
Yes, about that…
Ya, soal itu…
I tried to get in touch, but there were cops there.
Aku coba mendekat, tapi ada polisi di sana.
What?
Apa?
I ran away.
Aku kabur.
Hang on now.
Tunggu dulu.
Did you check if the cops tailed you?
Apa polisi membuntutimu?
It's fine!
Tidak!
Wait, did that high schooler just…
Tunggu, apa anak SMA itu…
Do we arrest him?
Apa kita tangkap dia?
No, he's probably a regular student.
Tidak, mungkin hanya siswa biasa.
-Let him go. -Let's go, then.
- Lepaskan saja. - Baik, ayo.
-Don't move! -Hey, wait!
- Jangan bergerak! - Hei, tunggu!
Stop right there!
Berhenti!
Wait!
Tunggu!
-Let me go! -Watch out!
- Lepaskan aku! - Awas!
This is obstruction of official duties!
Ini menghalangi tugas!
No! Help me!
Tidak! Tolong!
Who do you think--
Apa-apaan…
Regional Bureau of Health and Welfare, Narcotics Control Department.
Biro Kesehatan dan Kesejahteraan Regional, Departemen Pengawasan Narkotika.
Wait, where's Mr. Kurosaki?
Tunggu, di mana Pak Kurosaki?
Hey.
Hei.
You just left Yuzuki Apartments, right?
Kau dari Apartemen Yuzuki, 'kan?
What? No, I didn't.
Apa? Tidak.
Put your hands on that wall.
Letakkan tangan di dinding!
Okay.
Baik.
Shit!
Sial!
Nimble and flashy moves, but too sloppy.
Cepat dan bergaya, tapi terlalu ceroboh.
Is that it?
Itu saja?
Screw you.
Persetan.
Shit!
Sial!
All right.
Baiklah.
Arrest me, then.
Tangkap aku.
Ouch. What the hell, man?
Aduh! Apa-apaan?
Was it you who sold drugs to Keiichi Igarashi, the rapper?
Apa kau yang menjual narkoba pada raper Keiichi Igarashi?
Hey, are police detectives allowed to be this violent?
Hei, apa detektif polisi boleh sekejam ini?
I'm not a police detective. I'm a narcotics agent with the Ministry.
Aku bukan detektif polisi, tapi agen narkotika dari kementerian.
Narcotics agent?
Agen narkotika?
Talk when you feel like it.
Bicaralah jika sudah siap.
-About what? -Don't talk if you don't want to.
- Soal apa? - Jangan bicara jika tak mau.
About what, damn it!
Soal apa, sial?
Everything you know.
Semua yang kau ketahui.
I've got nothing.
Aku tak tahu apa-apa.
Too bad. Just one gram of meth makes for a lethal dose.
Sayang sekali. Satu gram sabu-sabu saja sudah bisa mematikan.
Hey, what are you doing back there?
Hei, kau sedang apa?
You're dead for sure if I inject this into you.
Kau pasti mati jika kusuntik dengan ini.
As if you would.
Kau tak akan berani.
That hurts!
Sakit!
Ouch.
Aduh.
Are you completely insane?!
Kau gila, ya?
Here goes.
Ini dia.
Stop! Don't put that in my body!
Hentikan! Jangan suntikkan itu!
Don't you sell this to your customers?
Bukankah kau menjual ini pada pelangganmu?
Wait, no.
Tunggu. Jangan.
You can't just kill a person.
Kau tak boleh asal membunuh orang.
No, I'm not going to kill anyone.
Aku tak membunuh orang.
It's common for drug dealers to die by overdosing on their own supply.
Pengedar narkoba sering mati karena barang mereka sendiri.
Don't move. You'll break the needle.
Jangan bergerak. Nanti jarumnya patah.
You're insane, you fucking psycho!
Kau gila! Dasar psikopat!
Yes, I'm insane.
Ya, aku memang gila.
I'll even become a "fucking psycho" against people like you drug dealers.
Aku bisa menjadi "psikopat" ketika melawan pengedar narkoba.
You're bluffing.
Kau menggertak.
No, I'm not.
Tidak.
Who's the one controlling your strings?
Siapa orang di balik jaringanmu?
No idea.
Tidak tahu.
Oh, yeah? Then die.
Benarkah? Maka, matilah.
Okay, I'll talk!
Baiklah, aku akan beri tahu!
I'll talk, damn it.
Aku akan beri tahu!
Who are you working for?
Kau bekerja untuk siapa?
Guy named Matsubara.
Namanya Matsubara.
There, I talked. Now, take out the needle.
Aku sudah bicara. Sekarang cabut suntikannya!
-Take it out! -Not yet.
- Cabut! - Belum.
Why? I already told you!
Kenapa? Aku sudah beri tahu!
I'll give you a chance.
Kuberi kau kesempatan.
What?
Apa?
I'll use your connection to Matsubara
Aku akan gunakan koneksimu ke Matsubara
and take down the drug cartel connected to Igarashi.
dan menjatuhkan kartel narkoba yang terkait dengan Igarashi.
I need you…
Aku mau kau…
to become my "S."
menjadi "M"-ku.
"S"?
"M"?
What's an S?
Apa itu "M"?
A spy.
Mata-mata.
What? Screw that. Why would I--
Apa? Tidak mau. Untuk apa aku…
Die here as a junkie or live on as my S.
Mati di sini sebagai pencandu atau hidup sebagai mata-mataku?
Decide right now.
Cepat pilih.
Okay.
Baiklah.
Okay, what?
Baiklah, apa?
I will…
Aku akan…
become your S.
menjadi M-mu.
If you run, you'll be a wanted man.
Jika kau kabur, kau akan diburu.
I'll leak to the criminal underworld that you were a spy.
Akan kubocorkan ke dunia kriminal bahwa kau adalah mata-mata.
They won't leave a traitor alive.
Mereka pasti membunuh pengkhianat.
Without a place in either world, you'll either die or go to prison.
Tanpa memilih pihak, kau akan mati atau masuk penjara.
Shit.
Sial.
You're mad.
Kau gila.
My enemies are mad.
Musuh-musuhku gila.
No choice but to be mad in turn.
Aku terpaksa harus gila juga.
Ouch.
Aduh.
But…
Tapi…
What exactly do you want me to do?
Kau mau aku melakukan apa?
You'll be my dog from today onwards.
Mulai hari ini, kau akan menjadi anjingku.
This is Hibiki Kaga's Resound! Info Catchman.
Inilah Suara Hibiki Kaga! Pencari Berita.
Next week, we'll take in the appeal of the Mikami Ginza shopping district
Pekan depan, kita akan mengulas daya tarik kawasan pertokoan Mikami Ginza
and catch, catch!
dan tangkap!
I said "catch," but here I am punching.
Kubilang, "tangkap", tapi aku malah memukul.
See you next week.
Sampai jumpa pekan depan.
And cut!
Cut!
-Nice. -Good work.
- Keren. - Kerja bagus.
-Was that good? -It was great.
- Apa sudah bagus? - Bagus.
Good. Looking sharp today.
Bagus. Hari ini keren.
-You think? -Excuse me.
- Serius? - Permisi.
-Can I get a picture with you? -Of course.
- Boleh minta foto? - Tentu.
-Thank you. -No problem.
- Terima kasih. - Sama-sama.
Your face looks much smaller in person.
Wajahmu jauh lebih kecil aslinya.
Really? I'm glad. Thanks.
Benarkah? Syukurlah. Terima kasih.
-May I? -Yes, of course.
- Berfoto, ya? - Tentu.
Here goes. Say cheese.
Ayo. Senyum.
-Okay! Thanks. -Thank you.
- Baik! Terima kasih. - Terima kasih.
-You a student? -Yes, at a nearby girls' college.
- Kau mahasiswi? - Ya, di kampus wanita dekat sini.
Really? Neat.
Benarkah? Keren.
Hey, I'm going to grab a bite. Want to join me?
Hei, aku mau makan. Kau mau ikut?
What?
Apa?
Really?
Serius?
-Absolutely. -May I?
- Serius. - Boleh?
Of course. Where's my phone again…
Tentu saja. Di mana ponselku…
Oh, I'll DM you.
Biar aku kirim pesan.
-DM? Sure. Later, then. -Okay.
- Kirim pesan? Tentu. Dah. - Baik.
The dealers we arrested all claim that their leader fled the scene right before.
Para pengedar yang ditangkap bilang pemimpinnya sudah kabur duluan.
Maybe he disguised himself as the high schooler you saw.
Mungkin dia menyamar menjadi siswa SMA yang kau lihat.
Kurosaki told us to let him be.
Kurosaki menyuruh kami melepaskannya.
Kurosaki?
Kurosaki?
I did not.
Tidak.
Don't just tell a bald-faced lie!
Jangan bohong terang-terangan!
You weren't on the scene when we raided them, right?
Kau tak ada di TKP saat penggerebekan, 'kan?
-Kurosaki? -I was there!
- Kurosaki? - Aku ada di sana!
Stop lying!
Jangan bohong!
Where were you?
Di mana kau?
Chasing the high schooler. But I lost him.
Mengejar siswa SMA itu. Tapi dia lolos.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Astaga.
Did the dealers give up their supplier?
Para pengedar itu bilang siapa pemasok mereka?
No, they all say that their leader was the only one in contact with the supplier.
Tidak, mereka bilang hanya pemimpin yang berkontak dengan pemasok.
Damn it.
Sialan.
If only you had caught that high schooler.
Andai saja kau berhasil menangkap anak SMA itu.
-I'll leave. -We--
- Aku pergi dulu. - Kita…
I'm still talking, Kurosaki!
Aku masih bicara, Kurosaki!
That's… That's an "Ah!"
Itu… Itu "Ah!"
Sorry about that.
Maaf, ya.
Not a problem.
Tidak masalah.
I ate some sea urchin while you were gone.
Tadi aku makan bulu babi saat kau pergi.
It's fresh and delicious.
Rasanya segar dan lezat.
Really?
Benarkah?
I'll have some, then.
Aku juga mau.
Premium sea urchin has a rather mature taste.
Bulu babi premium rasanya cukup matang.
Maybe a bit too mature for me.
Mungkin terlalu matang untukku.
Does it taste too much of alum?
Apa rasanya terlalu sepat?
Here, have some.
Ini, makanlah.
-Come on. -Wait a second.
- Ayo. - Tunggu sebentar.
Nice. Have some more.
Bagus. Tambah lagi.
I see she has cocaine circulating in her body.
Dia mabuk kokaina.
Should I give her some more?
Haruskah kuberikan lagi?
Hey, Aoi?
Hei, Aoi?
Have a sip of this delicious water.
Minumlah air lezat ini.
Meet Kaga and make him ingest cocaine.
Temui Kaga dan paksa dia mengonsumsi kokaina.
Get it on video.
Rekam.
I'll get killed if they find out I'm connected to you.
Aku bisa mati jika mereka tahu aku berhubungan denganmu.
MPD, Narcotics and Firearms Division, Akito Katsuragi.
MPD, Divisi Narkotika dan Senjata Api, Akito Katsuragi.
Why am I getting arrested?
Kenapa aku ditahan?
You're a dead man.
Matilah kau.
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO ACTUAL PERSONS, GROUPS, OR CASES IS PURELY COINCIDENTAL
SEGALA KEMIRIPAN DENGAN TOKOH, KELOMPOK, ATAU PERISTIWA NYATA HANYALAH KEBETULAN
Subtitle translation by: Saim Ul Hassan
Terjemahan subtitle oleh Mahesa